

# **MAYUR WAGHMODE**

## **DevOps Engineer**

## **My Contact**

 $\boxtimes$ 

waghmodemayur17@gmail.com

+91 72496 69807

•

Pune, Maharshtra

<u>My Portal</u>

in

LinkedIn

My Blogs

()

**GitHub** 

#### Skills

- DevOps Tools: Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift, Terraform, Ansible, Git, GitOps
- CI/CD: GitHub Actions, Tekton pipelines, Jenkins, CircleCI, Travis CI
- Cloud: AWS, IBM Cloud, Microsoft Azure
- Programming Languages: Python, Golang, Core Java, C++, C, Linux, Bash
- Frameworks: Spring Boot, Android, Flask

### **Certifications**

- Certified Kubernetes Administrator
- Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)
- <u>GitOps Fundamentals</u>

#### **Achievements**

- Persistent Bravo Individual Award (May 2022)
- Persistent Ace Individual Award (Feb. 2022)

#### **Other Details**

- **Soft Skills**: Team Player, Communication, Leadership, Optimistic
- Languages Known: English, Hindi, Marathi
- Hobbies: Playing Chess, Reading blogs

#### **About Me**

2+ Years of experience in DevOps

Experienced in using container and container orchestration tools – Docker, Podman, Buildah, Kubernetes, Openshift Proficient in writing CICD workflows for different solutions Building and testing open-source software, interacting with and contributing to open-source communities Certified Kubernetes Administrator from Linux Foundation Quick learner in adapting new skills, effective communication, and time management

## **Professional Experience**

#### Persistent Systems Limited, Pune | DevOps Engineer

NOV. 2020 - PRESENT

- · Key responsibilities:
  - Writing **CICD** workflows for building and publishing the container images, binaries
  - Automated the manual container certification, Preflight tool testing procedure using GitHub Actions, Travis CI
  - Building multi-architecture images using GitHub Actions/CirclCI/Tekton and buildah
  - Using **Terraform** for automating infrastructure provisioning
  - Containerizing applications using Docker/Buildah and ensuring successful deployment on Kubernetes cluster
  - Setup K8s cluster in HA with **Kubeadm** on ppc64le architecture
  - Worked on **Ansible** playbooks, **Bash** scripts to automate the manual tasks
  - Ported open-source softwares to support IBM ppc64le Operator Certification, Container certification, ArgoCD,
    kubelogin, Gomplate, KCP, Dex, Pipeline as Code, Syft, ec-cli
  - Maintainer of various images, binaries for IBM ppc64le

## Anubhooti Solutions, Pune | Flask Web Development Intern

DEC. 2018 - FEB. 2019

- · Key responsibilities:
  - Developed framework for Speech to Text application using **Flask**
  - Maintained user accounting details using SQLAIchemy

#### **Education**

#### BE, Computer Engineering, Pune University

PVG's College of Engineering and Technology, Pune August 2016 to October 2020

#### HSC, Maharashtra State Board

VPASC College, Baramati, Pune June 2015 to March 2016